bollywoodlover.com 2017-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Bollywood Lover

## Privacy Policy Of BollywoodLover.com

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

## **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your

## **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.

## **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

## **How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

**•** We only provide articles and information, we never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers.

### **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

### **Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

## **We collect your email address for:**

**Subscribe on our newsletter  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

## **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Simply contact through our Contact Us Page [Here ](http://bollywoodlover.com/contact-us/)

_Last Edited on 2015-10-21_
